Tomorrow, as in, like tomorrow?
Tomorrow, if you have time, of course.
I thought I could show you around town.
That sounds fun.
Wait, are you asking me out on a date?
Uh, I guess you could say that.
What do you say?
All right, I'll go on a date with you.
That's awesome. Is 10.30 okay?
We can meet by the station gates.
I'll see you there. Looking forward to it.
Mana Takamiya supposedly killed Kurumi Tokasaki.
We don't know why she's still alive.
Well, as long as she is still alive, we're sticking with the plan.
Tomorrow is a holiday, so there's no school.
Shido, we need you to ask Kurumiya on a date.
What? Even after what already happened?
It's because of what already happened.
There's no guarantee that she'll be revived if she gets killed again.
And let's not forget about Origami Tobeichi.
She will have told the AST, so they'll know that Kurumi didn't die.
Which means Mana knows as well.
All right, then.
I understand.
I'll get her to fall for me.
I swear it.
You swear what, exactly?
Oh!
Dating everyone at the same time.
It should be paradise.
This girl, that girl, and the girl over there could be yours.
Unfortunately, life doesn't always go the way we want.
Dating everyone at the same time.
Then you should be blessed.
Don't worry about how many andra's Pull out andнач Shanghai
You can either learn больше than a woman
Shut up and think That promo time
Da-da-da-d坂
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
I'm going to ask you one more time.
You're swearing what with Kurumi Tokusaki?
Uh, nothing. I don't know what you mean.
Just answer.
Trust me, this is very important.
Yeah, sorry. Gotta go. Tokus waiting.
I'll see you later.
Oh, origami. I must say, you look delicious, too.
Yes, very delicious.
But I think I might save you for later.
Instead, I'll devour you once I'm finished with Shido.
Oh, Shido.
I'm sorry about lunch, Toka.
But you got a chance to eat, right?
Yeah, I got to eat.
Where is he?
Boo, we only won two of these tickets instead of three.
Want to split the cost of one more?
Oh, hey, it's Toka.
Why haven't you eaten lunch yet?
Oh, no, what's wrong?
Tell us everything. Who did what?
Shido isn't here.
And then I started thinking about how...
Well, I started thinking about how we haven't really talked that much today.
And then I, uh...
For some reason, I just got sad.
Girl, you do not have to say another word!
Shido's a jerk!
And he's taking you for granted!
That is just so lame!
No, really. He didn't do anything wrong.
No, no, of course not.
But still, you don't have to be sad, and we can help.
We've got some time before dinner.
Don't you want to go home first?
Hey, Toka?
Are you okay?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
I am very confused!
Okay, what's going on?
Shoot, this isn't working.
What's next?
Shido.
Hi.
I have a question for you.
Uh, yeah?
Tomorrow, will you go on a date with me, please?
What?
A date, huh?
Pretty, please.
Yeah, sure thing.
How wonderful!
Those girls were right about everything!
Now then, meet me by the statue in front of the station at 10 a.m.
And don't forget!
What's this?
It's Origami.
Hey there, Origami, what's up?
Are you okay?
I'm fine, but you shouldn't be left alone right now.
I will be waiting for you at the fountain in front of the station tomorrow at exactly 11 a.m.
Wait, but I...
But I...
Crap.
Test, test, can you hear me?
I can't believe you're triple booked on such an unbelievably important day, you dirty little dog.
Hey, don't be mean.
Remember, you're the one who kept me from canceling.
If you don't keep promises you make to Toka, her happiness meter will go down.
And if you cancel with Origami, she'll be even more suspicious than she already is.
Stop worrying.
You're not by yourself.
We'll be supporting you with everything we've got.
All you have to do is follow the schedule and go with the flow.
Commander, the plan will commence shortly.
Countdown is beginning now.
First, I'm going to the aquarium with Toka, right?
I know you can do it, Cheeto.
It's dangerous, so don't get hurt!
Right.
Three, two, one.
Now, let's start our date, shall we?
The date has begun.
Cheeto!
Great.
She's here.
I chose her outfit.
Not too bad, huh?
You all right?
Those clothes, they, um, they look really cute.
Who cares about stupid clothes?
Can we just go now?
Sure, but do you even know where you're going?
Not the best start, but it could have been worse.
Commander, look!
It's Origami.
I thought she wasn't supposed to get here until 11.
Apparently, she's impatient.
So I've been wondering, what is this aquarium thing?
Wait, you don't know?
Why'd you want to come here if you didn't know what it was?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I just wanted to go out on a date with you.
It didn't matter what it was.
An aquarium's a place that has lots of fish and stuff that lives in water.
Really?
Do you think they'll have fried fish?
No.
What about boiled fish?
Or poached fish?
Or steamed fish?
The only thing you ever think about is food.
You'll know it when you see it.
The main target has a piece.
Well, at least this one's just ten minutes early.
I can't believe this place is real!
Try to use your inside voice.
Right.
Sorry.
I can't help myself.
This is the neatest thing ever.
Those are really real fish out there.
Yeah.
More than just fish.
Wow.
It's all so beautiful.
Come with me.
I want to go see the rest.
Hey, Shido.
It's almost time for you to meet with Kurami.
What?
Already?
We'll pick you up using Fraxinus, so go outside and find somewhere with no one around.
Are you coming?
Because you haven't moved a bit.
Oh, no.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
Only my stomach.
I'm going to head to the bathroom.
Keep looking at the fish for a while.
What?
But are you going to be okay?
I need to find a place where no one's around.
Retrieval.
Welcome to the gates in front of the station.
Now.
Hold on.
Already?
Sorry, I'm late.
Don't worry.
I actually only got here around a minute ago myself.
So, where shall we go first?
Let me think.
This is where the real game begins.
All right, everyone.
Make your selections.
I think it should be number two.
And then their hands can touch during a romantic movie moment.
That would be so sweet.
Option one is the obvious choice.
All girls love shopping, so I really can't go wrong.
Neither one of those are technically bad.
Except they are both attached to the station, and the aquarium is attached as well.
So the risk of running into another girl is pretty low.
But I always say there's no reason to go looking for trouble.
Really?
So a lingerie store is our best bet?
Well, the other day, Shido asked her to show her panties.
She didn't seem to have a problem with it.
What?
A lingerie store for real?
Quit being so loud, pervert!
Oh!
If that's what you want, I don't mind going to one of those stores.
She took the bait and ran with it!
She's so bold.
Then let's go!
It'll be your job to help me choose something cute.
Wow, there's so much hair for me to try on.
Which one do you think would look best on me?
Selections, everyone!
This is the time to attack.
Extreme flattery is sure to reduce any resistance to the kiss.
Yeah, I mean, she was okay going to the store.
So it's probably a good call to go for it, okay, Shido?
I, uh, they're both really pretty.
But, uh, I like that style over there.
You like the black one, and you think it's better than these two?
Yeah, just because, you know, I think you'd look great in it!
Well, that's very sweet of you to say.
I'll try it on so we'll know for sure.
Cool, that sounds great.
Just make it quick, okay?
So, how do I look?
What do you think you're doing, mister?
We have an emergency!
Why is this loser with Kermi?
Good question.
And what's with the lingerie?
That's so lame!
Okay, Shido, it's time.
Get out of there now.
But make sure you don't leave Kermi hanging.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, my stomach!
Kermi, I'm going to the restroom.
I'll catch up with you in a bit, okay?
Also, you're looking frickin' credible!
Wow.
Hey, where are you going?
Get back here right now!
You are so lame!
Make revisions to the schedule.
Oh, Shido, this is just the beginning.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Don't worry about it.
I just got here myself.
You look kind of sleepy.
No, no, I'm not tired at all.
So where did, uh, where did you want to go?
To the movies.
But you don't want to go to the one here, right?
Of course, silly.
We have to go to this one.
I've already picked up tickets.
This isn't good.
That one's not any better.
Okay.
I'll be back in just a bit.
Lunch?
We have just enough time to eat before the movie.
I figured now would be as good a time as any.
Sure.
Let's eat then.
Hey, Origami.
Why did you ask me out on a date today?
I just didn't want you to be by yourself.
Once the movie's over, come back to my place.
Uh, your place?
What for?
Look, you should stay with me for a while.
I'm very serious.
Here you go, guys.
There's something so weird about her.
Commander, it's Toka.
Ah, shoot.
Want me to heimlich you?
No, thanks.
I'll be right back.
Hey!
Toka!
There you are!
I was getting really worried.
Yeah, me too.
Do you want to get something to eat?
Yes, that sounds perfect.
I'm so hungry.
Man, that sure is a lot of sushi.
Especially after a little wary.
Oh, my fiddle metal!
You really bought it?
That face the underwear?
Well, after you told me I looked in freaking credible in it,
I kind of had to.
Yeah.
It's not the underwear!
It's the underwear!
It's the way!
Which room should we get?
They'll be seen!
You used to eat also.
Evil.
Wait.
WTF?
Wow!
I'm so sorry for you.
What?
No.
Hang that hard.
Wait.
No.
Wish that hurt.
I'm so sorry.
Stop!
No.
It's fun!
Hahahaha!
Keep it worked!
You did splash!
They made you engine.
No big him.
Yeah!
Get up the ocean now.
Looks like it's nap time.
You worked pretty hard.
Sorry, Corony. Bathroom!
What is wrong with that kid?
He's hardly making this a stellar date.
I wonder where he keeps rushing off to anyway.
Oh, well, it doesn't matter, I suppose.
After all, I'm sure little Shido will be mine soon enough.
I get warm and tingly just thinking about it.
Not long, and then he will be mine.
Oh, this guy's a feisty one.
Oh, man, my turn is good.
Look how close it is.
Oh, it's time to wait now.
Oh, look at you.
It seems like I found a few boys who are up to something interesting.
Calm down.
Don't worry about me.
I'd like to get in on this sweet action, if that's okay.
Believe it or not, I've been known to be fairly decent with a gun myself.
What should we do?
Um, heh, heh, yeah, that is, sweetheart.
Wow, thanks so much for your permission.
I certainly didn't expect that eager welcome, so it is appreciated.
But I have a small suggestion.
Why don't we change the rules?
For fun.
It's not that complicated.
We'll just switch targets for a little while.
Hey, what happened?
Is it broken?
Get that thing fixed!
What are we missing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it was my fault.
I should have been paying attention.
It's you, stupid origami.
What the heck are you doing here?
Well, stupid Toka, what I do is none of your business.
That's fine.
I don't have time to waste on a loser like you anyway, so there.
Good, because neither do I.
Because I'm actually on my way to find Shido.
Ha!
Whatever, I'm on a date with Shido right now, so you need to stop telling lies.
You're lying.
Shido happens to be on a date with me.
Oh, no.
This could be bad.
Who is he with right now?
Hey, come back here!
I'm not done yelling at you yet!
Shido, bad news.
We've lost Kurami.
How could you lose her?
Alert!
Spirit wave reaction nearby.
It's in the woods by the park's east exit.
Shido, calm down!
Shido!
Oh, my.
Hello, Shido.
I'm so glad you finally decided to join us.
Help!
Please!
She's a monster!
You have to help me!
Don't let her kill me!
You tried to kill something without being ready to be killed yourself.
Doesn't that seem odd to you?
It was helpless, and now you are helpless.
How do you like looking down the barrel of a gun?
Oh, no, my finger must have slipped.
Shido, get out of there!
Where do you think you're going, Shido?
Let go of me!
Oh, woe is me.
I can't believe it.
I've completely messed things up.
I was having such a wonderful time on our date together.
I wanted it to last a little longer.
Oh, well.
I can't be helped now.
Are you alright, big brother?
Mana?
I don't know.